Rohit Sharma

Summer Intern at Indian Institute of Technology, Guwahati

rohitkumarsharma221@gmail.com

Summary

Hello, I'm 3rd year undergraduate student at Netaji Subhash Engineering College, Kolkata in computer science and engineering Department.

I am interested in programming and research based projects in the field of Network Security and machine learning.

I have worked as Summer intern on Intrusion Detection System at Indian Institute of Technology, Guwahati.

Presently, I am focusing on learning Machine Learning optimisation techniques, Design analysis and algorithms along with Python and Java.

Experience

Assistant Team Head

April 2017 - Present

I was appointed as Assistant Team Head for our event web-o-tronics in college technical fest(Avenir).

Summer Intern at Indian Institute of Technology, Guwahati

June 2017 - July 2017 (2 months)

Education

Netaji Subhash Engineering College 109

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Science, 2015 - 2019

Kendriya Vidyalaya

Senior Secondary, PCM, 2012 - 2014

Kendriya Vidyalaya

High School, Junior High/Intermediate/Middle School Education and Teaching, 2003 - 2012

Honors and Awards

Secured 1st Rank in Dare-2-code Competition.

Rohit Sharma

Summer Intern at Indian Institute of Technology, Guwahati

rohitkumarsharma221@gmail.com



Contact Rohit on LinkedIn